现在，我们将设置一些有趣的界面了
All right. So this is where things start to get
到目前为止还都没介绍什么有趣的内容
fun if you have not been having fun already.
我们将构建这个视图
So what we are going to do now is build out this view.
相当于一个实时详情视图
You will notice here that what we are doing is this is kind of like a live detailed view.
我们将从手机中获取信息
What we are doing is we are pulling information
并渲染该视图
from the phone in order to render this view.
它会显示我们正朝着哪个方向前进
So it shows which way we are heading,
海拔是多少，当前移动速度是多少
the altitude, the current speed.
所有这些信息都来自于手机
All of this is going to be coming from your phone.
因此，我们需要
So in order to do that, we actually need to go ahead and
使用手机的 API 来获得这些信息
use the phone's API to get that information.
顺便提醒下，如果你尝试在 Android 模拟器上跟着操作
And one side note, if you are trying to do this on Android in the
可能会因为某些原因而出现故障
simulator,is probably not going to work for some reason.
Android 模拟器不能实现我们要执行的操作
The Android simulator does not work with what we are doing,
但是如果你在实际设备上使用 Expo 应用，则一切正常
but if you have it on a actual real device using the Expo app, you will be fine.
因此请别使用 Android 模拟器，而是使用 Expo 应用
So you either forget about the Android emulator and use the Expo app
或 iOS 模拟器。我们开始吧
or the iOS simulator. All right. Let us jump into it.
转到此处
So what we are going to do is,
新建一个视图文件，叫做 Live.js
this new view is going to be called Live.js.
暂时先导入
What we are going to have for now is
react，
just react in a component and then we will import the View,
然后导入 View、Text 以及 ActivityIndicator
Text and this thing called ActivityIndicator,
都来自于 react-native
which are all coming from react-native.
然后导出这个扩展自 component 的类
And then we will go ahead and export this class which extends component.
设定此组件的状态
So what state this component is going to have,
包括坐标，暂时设为 null
it is going to have some coordinates which are set to null initially.
还包括 status，也设为 null
It is going to have a status which we will also set to
以及 direction，设为空字符串
null and a direction which is just going to be an empty string.
我们可以从 this.state 上获取这些信息
So what we can do is we can grab this information off of the state.
我们将获取几个不同的视图
And then there are a few different views that we are going to get
具体取决于你所获得的权限
depending on the specific permissions that you are granted.
如果 status === null
So what we are going to say is if status equals null,
表示用户尚未授予任何权限
so the user really has not given us any permissions yet,
依然保持默认状态
nothing has changed from the default state,
则渲染 ActivityIndicator
then what we want to do is render an ActivityIndicator,
并将 marginTop 设为 30
and we will give it a margin top of 30.
ActivityIndicator 中的内容只是表示正在加载的旋转图标
All in ActivityIndicator is it's basically a loading spinners.
你之前见过，它只是在渲染旋转图标
So you've seen it before. It's just going render a spinner like,
仿佛在提示系统正在等待中
"Hey, we are waiting on something."
如果 status === denied
If the status equals denied,
表示你请求了权限，但是遭到用户拒绝
meaning you asked for permission and they did not give it to you,
我们暂时渲染一个视图，在其中显示文本“Denied”
what we are going to do for now is just render a view with some text in that says denied,
然后我们将执行完全一样的操作
and then we are going to do this exact same thing,
但是这里的 denied
but instead of denied,
将改为 undetermined
it is going to be for undetermined.
当你在模拟器中操作时
And when you are messing around with the simulator, again,
某些权限会比较卡顿
some of these permissions are going to be a little bit
因为我们没有在实际设备上操作
wonky because we are not on an actual real device,
但是可以实现最终目标
but we will get to that when we get to that.
最后，如果不是 denied 或 undetermined
And then lastly, if it is not denied or undetermined,
则表明授予了权限
that means it was granted.
我们将
So what we will say is,
渲染一个视图
we will render a view,
暂时
and then for now,
我们将渲染几个文本组件
what we are going to do is we will render a few text components.
暂时显示这个状态
We will just go ahead and show the state for now,
看起来不错
and this looks pretty good.
我们将这个当做新的标签页添加进来
So let us go ahead and add this as a new tab.
转到 App.js
So inside of App.js,
首先需要导入该组件
first, we need to import it.
接着，转到 Tabs 中
And next, what we need to do is inside of tabs,
添加一个新的属性
let us go ahead and add any property.
称之为 Live
We will call it Live,
就像之前一样
and just as we have done before,
screen 设为 Live 组件
screen is going to be the Live component.
添加一些导航选项
Some options here, the tabBarLabe,
将 tabBarLabel 设为 Live
we're just going to just say Live,
然后复制这段代码
and then I am actually just going to copy
因为我们将使用 Ionicon 字体
this one because we are also going to use Ionicon font,
但是将 name 改为 ios-speedometer
but the name of this one is going to be ios-speedometer.
看看是否可行
All right, let us see if this is working.
转到 Live
So we got a Live.
注意，这里出现了旋转指示符
Notice, we get an indicator.
因为当前 status 设为 null
That is because the current status is set to null,
我们假设可行
so we can just assume that this is working for sure.
当然可以设为 denied
We can set it to denied.
现在应该能在这里看到 denied
Now, what we should see it is denied up here.
重新设为 null
All right. Let's set this back to null,
我们将在后续视频中继续完善这一部分
and we will continue building this out in future videos.